CURRICULUM VITAE

SANDIP. A. SANTRA

Address:

M/49/294 Pragatinagar, Naranpura, Ahmedabad-380013. Contact Details:

Ph.:+91 8905989129.

E-mail:santrasandip7@gmail.com

CAREER OBJECTIVE

A growth oriented and challenging position in a progressive and prestigious organization, Rich knowledge of banking industry with 4 years of experience in handling operations as well as sales, where my skills are utilized in a best way with a scope of learning, innovation and all-round career development.

COMPETENCIES

- Having excellent working knowledge of banking products like mortgages, insurance, current accounts etc.
- Comprehensive knowledge of banking sector regulatory and legal requirements.
- Experience of data mining and large-scale customer database data interrogation and manipulation.
- Monitoring lending transactions for accuracy and company compliance.
- Ability to plan and deliver effective sales strategies.
- Arranging networking events with local businesses and representing the bank at these and promoting its services and products.
- Accepting overall responsibility for the banks products like: personal loans, credit cards, unsecured loans and overdrafts

ACADAMIC CREDENTIALS

Educational Qualifications

- Have passed 10th std. from GSEB board with 71% in English medium in 2004.
- Have passed 12th std. from GSEB board with 69% in English medium in 2006.
- Have done B.COM graduation from Gujarat University in English medium in 2010.

ACHIEVEMENTS

- Achieved Annual Li target of 2015/16 for the Branch within 2 months and became the 1st Branch in the zone to achieve annual target by 300%.
- Qualified in several contest and felicitated with Awards.

WORKING EXPERIENCE

- Worked with Kingfisher Airlines as a Guest Service Officer from May 2011 to February 2012.
- Worked with Kotak Mahindra Bank as an Assistant Acquisition Manager from March 2012 to October 2014.
- Working with HDFC Bank as a Branch Manager from October 2014 to till date.

CERTIFICATE OF PARTICIPATION

- Have done a SWIFT JYOTI course from NIIT.
- Have done a Banking and Sales Management course from ITM Edutech Training Pvt. Ltd.
- Have done AMFI certification.
- Have done IRDA certification.

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Father's Name : Mr. A. G. Santra
Mother's Name : Mrs. R. A. Santra
Date Of Birth : 09th July 1987
Marital Status : Married

Sex : Male

Strengths : Punctual, Confident and Self Motivator **Languages Known** : English, Hindi, Gujarati and Bengali.

Areas of Interest: Traveling, Net-Surfing, Making Friends, Playing Guitar.

Declaration

I hereby affirm that the information furnished by me is correct and nothing has been concealed.

Date: Place:

(S. A. SANTRA)